foreclosuredeals.com 2018-05-22

# Privacy and Policies Provided by ForeclosureDeals.com

Foreclosuredeals.com is committed to actively respecting and protecting your personal information in all of our online and offline procedures and processes. This document will explain our Privacy and Information Security Policy, as well as some of the steps we take to maintain your privacy and security when you use our website.

## Types of Personal Information

We collect two main types of information from our members. The first type of information we collect includes personal information supplied by members during the registration process. The second type includes information supplied by you when you add a property to our foreclosure listings.

## Personal Information

We define personal information as any information about yourself, supplied by you, when either registering as a new member, updating your membership profile, or listing a property for sale, as well as statistical information collected regarding your usage of our website and online services. Statistical website usage information typically includes data such as the length of time you are logged on to our site and which areas of our site you spent the most time viewing or searching. This information helps us to establish usage patterns and adjust our site to bring you a more robust and user-friendly online experience.

## IP Address

Your Internet Protocol (IP) address is unique to your internet network connection. IP addresses are used to identify both the sender of information as well as the receiver of information. We collect IP addresses only from users that send us an email via our Contact Us pages. We do not report any IP addresses to advertisers.

## Information Security

Your security is extremely important to us. Here at Foreclosuredeals.com, we safeguard your personal information using the same secure infrastructure that protects our proprietary property database. Once your username and password information is stored, access is achieved only by Foreclosuredeals.com employees who have access to our secure property database. This security infrastructure is constantly monitored for best practices and updated to meet our high standards of online information protection. Foreclosuredeals.com does not store any of your credit information. All credit information is processed by CCBill's secure credit processing website. Please review CCBill's Privacy Policy by [clicking here](http://www.ccbill.com/cs/acf/html/privacy_policy-english.html). Foreclosuredeals.com is not responsible for the security practices or policies of any vendors, advertisers, or third-party service providers.

## Nondisclosure

Except as noted within this document, or as expressly agreed upon by you, Foreclosuredeals.com does not share or disclose any of your individual personal information with any vendors, advertisers, or third-party service providers. Foreclosuredeals.com is not responsible for the privacy or information disclosure policies of any vendors, advertisers, or third-party service providers.

## Privacy & Cookie Policy

Foreclosuredeals.com holds the privacy of our customers and members as one of our chief concerns. Below you will find details on how we strive to keep our customers safe and secure, as well as details on how we handle and protect your personal information. Like almost all other websites, this website uses log files to store certain data. Information found in a log file includes information about user visits to our page, such as IP address, the type of browser used, your internet service provider, time and date stamps of your visits, number of clicks and page views, and referring and exit pages. This information helps us better understand our user demographic by analyzing trends and tracking where people seem to be going on our site. However, none of this information is linked to any personal information or any other data which may be used to identify individual users. Our log files are kept safe and securely encrypted within our system, and we use them solely for our own informational purposes.

This website does use cookies to store information about individual user preferences, record data on which pages users access, to customize the user experience based on browser type, and record other information the user's browser transmits. We do not share this information with outside parties.

To help keep your membership cost as low as possible, we use third party advertising companies like [Google to serve ads when you visit our website](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/). These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third parties which advertise on our site, including Google, may use cookies of their own. When you click on ad links, these services automatically receive information from your browser (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number), such as your IP address, and may use technologies such as cookies, web beacons or JavaScript to judge the effectiveness of their ad campaigns or to personalize ad content. This website has no control over the use of cookies or such technology by third party advertisers.

As a third party vendor, Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to serve ads on our site based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. To learn more about advertising and your privacy, or to opt out of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. You can also disable cookies through your browser and disallow this kind of information collection. You can learn more about this by consulting the help guide for your specific internet browser.

## Thank You

We value your patronage and appreciate the time you have taken to read this Privacy and Security Policy. We are serious about personal privacy, and we are committed to staying abreast of the latest technological advancements in the field of digital privacy and protection. Foreclosuredeals.com reserves the right to update, modify or amend this Privacy and Security Policy at any time. When we update, modify or amend this policy, we will post the updated version to this web page. You are responsible for visiting this page on a regular basis so that you can view the most current version of our policy. We also urge you to read our Terms and Conditions of Use. If you have any questions whatsoever regarding our Privacy and Security Policy, please do not hesitate to contact our support staff by clicking on [Contact Us](https://www.foreclosuredeals.com/contact.php).
